>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 现在我们有了基础。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
now we have the foundation in place.
我们可以理解我们在说什么
We can understand what
object we're talking about
当我们绑定到这个关键词的时候
when we bind to this key word.
让我们看看我们能做些什么
Let's look at what we can do with it.
我们将首先关注类模式，因为它是
We're gonna to focus first on
the class pattern since it is
在 JavaScript 中使用的最常见的模式。
by far the most prevalent
pattern used in JavaScript.
类关键字是在顶部的表面语法糖。
The class keyword is ostensibly
syntactic sugar layered on top of
我们接下来要了解的原型系统
the prototype system,
which we will learn about next.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这就是它的样子。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So
here's what it looks like.
我们使用类关键字，使用类关键字的名称。
We use a class keyword,
we use a name for the class keyword.
顺便说一下，这是一个有点了解的事实。
By the way, this is a little know fact.
类不必是语句，类可以是表达式，并且
Classes don't have to be statements,
classes can be expressions, and
他们可以是匿名的
they can be anonymous.
我不认为你应该去做匿名的课
I don't ever think you should do
an anonymous class expression but
这其实是件事
that is actually a thing.
可以使用或不使用扩展子句来定义类。
Classes can be defined with or
without an extends clause.
在这里，我们只是在定义一个不延伸任何东西的等级，所以
Here, we're just defining a class
that doesn't extend anything, so
是顶级类别的
it's the top level class.
如果需要，您可以选择定义构造函数，如我们在第 2 行上做的那样，
You can choose to define a constructor
if you want, like we're doing on line 2,
并且您可以添加方法。
and you can add methods.
请看第四行，我们甚至不需要它们之间的逗号。
And look on line 4,
we don't even need commas in between them.
他们创造了一个绝妙的工作
They did a fantastic job of just
dribbling all kinds of syntactic sugar
在此功能部件上。
on this feature.
很有吸引力
It's very attractive.
然后我们看第 10 行它看起来就像在任何其他的
Then we look at line 10, it looks exactly
like instantiating classes in any other
面向类的语言。
class oriented language.
我们刚刚说了新的，资本 W 的讲习班，我们得到了一个例子。
We just say new, capital W Workshop,
and we get an instance.
我们调用 deepJS.ask 和方法调用工作。
And we call deepJS.ask and
the method call works.
有一个这样的背景是有效的。
And there's a this context that works.
这就是阶级语法的样子。
So that's what the class
syntax looks like.
如果要将一个类扩展至另一个类，
If you want to extend one
class into another class,
在第 10 行的范围内使用扩展子句。
you use the extends clause
like here on line 10.
你不用重新定义任何其他方法
You don't have to redefine
any other methods that
已定义，因为它们将被称为继承。
are already defined because they'll be so
called inherited.
因此，您可以在第 11 行上定义类似 speakUp 方法的新方法，并且
So you can define new methods like
the speakUp method here on line 11 and
当您实例化该子代类时，可以调用第 18 行，
when you instantiate that Child class,
you can then invoke line 18,
你可以用这个方法，点说话，就像在对象上一样。
you can invoke that method, dot speak up,
exactly like it was on the object.
事实上，阶级制度现在也有一个超级关键词，
As a matter of fact, the class system
also now has a super keyword in it,
允许你做相对多态的多态性
which allows you to do
relative polymorphism.
如果您具有定义与父类同名的方法的子类，
If you have a child class that defines a
method of the same name as a parent class,
所以被称为 " 影子"
so called shadowing.
如果您有一个定义与父代中相同的方法名的方法名。
If you have one that defines the same
method name in a child as in the parent.
您可以引用子代中的父代
You can refer to the parent from the child
就像你在 12 线上看到的那样
by saying super dot,
like you see on line 12.
>> Kyle Simpson: 顺便说，这是扩展以外的示例
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: By the way,
this is an example of extension beyond
语法糖，因为在 ES6 类之前
syntactic sugar because
prior to ES6 classes,
基本上没有办法做相对多态的多态性。
there was essentially no way
to do relative polymorphism.
不存在与超级关键字等同的值。
There was no equivalent
of the super keyword.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不是说这是不好的事，我只是说，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I'm not saying
that's a bad thing, I'm just saying,
当人们说这只是语法上的糖分，不是，不是。
when people say, it's just syntactic
sugar anyway, no, it isn't.
它是自己的机制，有自己的复杂性。
It's its whole own mechanism,
with its own set of complexities.
如果你把注意力集中在任何东西上就会有一大堆东西
And if you pay attention to the specs
at all, there's a whole bunch of stuff,
就像一列大型货运火车去上课
like a big freight train headed for
classes.
它会以各种新的复杂，私人和公共领域的形式爆炸
It's gonna explode with all kinds of new
complexity, private and public fields, and
私人和公共的方法以及其他的装饰和装饰
private and public methods, and
all these others, decorators and
都是些其他的东西
all this other stuff.
因此，类是其自身的复杂性同步。
So classes are their own complexity sync.
他们会得到各种新的功能
They're gonna get all kinds of
new features added into them.
就像现在语言里的一种语言，不仅仅是语法上的糖分，
It's like a language within a language at
this point, it's not just syntactic sugar,
但这对于这些最简单的例子来说是有用的
but that is a useful, mental model for
these simplest of examples.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不得不说，虽然有很多句法
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I do have to say that
even though there's a bunch of syntactic
糖根本没有改变什么
sugar, they didn't change
anything fundamentally about how
函数调用工作以及该关键字的绑定方式。
function calls work and
how that this keyword gets bound.
因此，即使您在类实例上定义方法，
So, even if you define
a method on a class instance,
如果你把它传递到这个超时值中，猜测是什么 ?
if you pass it into a said timeout,
guess what?
它会失去它的束缚
It's gonna lose its this binding.
他们不会在某种程度上自动地自动绑定。
They're not somehow magically auto bound.
那些在课堂上的功能
Those functions on class,
类实例上的方法与任何其他函数一样。
the methods on class instances,
behave just like any other function.
有很多开发商对这一决定感到不满
And there are a lot of developers
that were upset at that decision,
他们还真想让 JavaScript 更进一步
they really wanted JavaScript to go
one step further and force class
用于在正常类或正常类中自动绑定的方法
methods to be sort of autobound
the way they are in normal class or
以更传统的语言来定位语言
in more traditional class
orientated languages.
这个方法的一个自动约束的想法就是为什么在这个过渡时期
And that idea of having an autobound this
method is why in this interim period for
过去几年我们目睹了
the last several years, we have
seen an explosion of patterns where
人们想要硬的或自动的方法，并且不是自动的。
people want hardbound or autobound
methods and they aren't automatically.
所以你看到的很多事情都像是第四行
So what you see a lot happening
is something like line four,
而不是在原型上定义一个方法
where instead of defining a method
on the prototype, we added into
构造函数，使用硬绑定方法或使用箭头函数，好吗 ?
the constructor and use a hardbound
method or use an arrow function, okay?
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这让我深深的困扰着这个成语的传播。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: This deeply troubles me
to see this propagation of this idiom.
这想法是很难受的
This idea that it's got to be hard bound.
我不想给它带来任何动力所以我要用一个词法
I don't want any dynamism to it all,
so I'm gonna use a lexical this
或者我要用一个硬的界限来完成这个任务
from an arrow function or I'm gonna use
a hard bound function to accomplish that.
因为你本质上是背叛了阶级所建立的整个体系。
Because you are essentially betraying the
entire system that classes has built upon.
整个类系统基于此构想，即您的方法不存在
The entire class system is built upon this
idea that your methods don't exist on
您的实例，它们存在于您的原型上，并且
your instances,
they exist on your prototypes and
你猜你说的时候会发生什么然后你给它分配一个功能
guess what happens when you say
this.ask and you assign it a function?
现在已经不再是样机了，就在你的例子里。
It's no longer on the prototype anymore,
it's on your instance.
所以每次你把一个功能都实例化了，你就会得到一个完整的
So every single time you instantiate
a function, you're getting a whole
将所有这些函数的副本单独复制到每个实例。
separate copy of all those functions
added to every single instance.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这不是特别可怕的
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It's not that
that is particularly terrible for
性能的 cuz JavaScript 引擎其实挺不错的
performance cuz JavaScript engines
are actually pretty good at it.
我有个真正的问题就是
The real problem I have with that is it's
就像我们在这个关键词中所说的那样
exactly like we talked
about in this key word.
你将会尽一切努力来完成这一联合战术
You're going to all the trouble
to do all this syntactic juggling
让自己成为一个具有超级动态的关键字的等级系统。
to get yourself a class system with
this key word that can be super dynamic.
猜猜你刚刚创造了什么，一个非常糟糕的模块。
And guess what you just created,
a really terrible version of the module.
一个令人困惑，丑陋的词汇模块的脆弱版本。
A really confusing, and ugly, and
brittle version of a lexical module.
我们有 20 多年的词法模块模式。
We've had lexical module pattern for
20 plus years.
我们应该拥抱和拥抱
And we ought to just be embracing and
语言中已存在的内容。
using what was already
there in the language.
这并不是说阶级制度没有好处。
That's not to say there's no
benefit to the class system.
肯定有好处。
There are definitely benefits.
如果你真的想做多态和多重的遗产
If you really wanna do polymorphism and
multiple levels of inheritance and
超级大的
super and all that.
分类系统非常好。
The class system is great.
只是绝大多数人都在使用这个类系统
It's just that the vast majority of
people that are using the class system,
最终彻底切断它的膝盖
end up completely cutting
it off at its knees.
割掉它的膝盖，失去所有的动态灵活性，
Cutting it off its knees, losing all
the dynamic flexibility, and getting
他们所拥有的模块模式的一个非常糟糕的版本
a really terrible version of what they
could have had with the module pattern.